Ajay, do
Ajay,
that accused, welcome back to another video,
electricity fitting, and in today's video, we are going to
talk about such investments,
Paytm, by following the strategy,
any person can easily
earn 15 to 20 percent from the market, that is within six
red spots and we will learn
about some indicators which will help us in getting
entry points for any stock, in
this stage I have paid
attention to the rules of money,
which we discussed in the previous video,
so if you have not seen this video then
definitely watch this video, and so let's start, in the
stock
exchanges that have come up in India, whether it is Naseeb or BSE, there are
forty companies listed there, and it is
a very
serious and very difficult task for any person to get even 450 companies under the delivery system, so I have
prepared a list by filtering and making the top leading companies of every sector,
and while filtering, I paid attention to
their capital employed, return on capital title,
Clinton equity, their updates, DSC, their  The
topic is about his leadership and I have focused on the
fourth law of money,
I have considered three sectors, the
sectors of which I feel I have knowledge,
so you can also divide the increase according to yourself, you
can modify it,
but you have to pay attention, you have to press only those
companies and press those companies which have grown
consistently in the said sector,
I have taken these companies, large
cap and mid cap, after completing chapter 6, the
selection is very simple, you simply,
like the selection of a cricket team, the
selection of the Indian cricket team, there are
lakhs of cricketers who are
playing cricket in India, but it is
very difficult for the BCCI, which is the board of the cricket team, to audit all these cards, so what
they do is that they
keep an eye on the quantity on their Play Store and they have to prepare the team,
prepare a squad, it was 15, for the
last test series, for an ODI
series, Prabhu prepares 19400  From
within, Antil has seen that some such
plain pepper can be very uniform proof.
He cannot perform very well for a team, only
then can he
control that player. So what you have to do is,
when you do not find such a stock, then
you have to work only on this list.
Now, if you want to add or remove any stock from this,
then also you
can follow this strategy. If someone has
performed consistently well, then you
can add that stop to this list, which
can remove the accumulated stop from there. Simple, so what you have to do is you have to go to
Google,
after going to Google, you have to type 'Trading
U
A Testing', after going to
this first link, I have clicked on the diet chart, if you click on the
answer chat, then
this chart will open for you, whether it is
of any company or any index, then
you have to go to indicators,
next you have to click on
indicators, let you apply indicators, one
is radish, other is
hum  Moving average also that explanation and
movie avengers simple moving average and you have to
apply it and like this,
after applying this indicator you
can plan for it and in this
you have to do some notifications in the movie watching indicator, you
will click on the top setting, do not pay attention
that you will apply it because I want daddy
moving average up-to-date movie app, it tells
me the average price of the stock in the last one day
and it
itself tells you how the stock is trading now,
that is the YouTube curved oversold
zone and where is the current stock right now,
you will be able to see it on the right side, it is
amazing, you will be able to
see this list
of companies which I have considered,
I considered Swiss company in which
Reliance, TCS, Infosys, HCL, Instant
Bonus for Britain or all these
companies of my tractor, now Sukh Top
Monopoly, which is a top online company,
I have printed out all of them here,
TC, Colgate, HDFC  Banks like ICICI
Bank are all appointment companies.
So, what you have to do is to
check these companies one by one to see
which stocks are
available under their respective white 2014 bridge or near it, and all
districts including Jinnah etc. are available in their wild straights.
When a company's stock price is
below its 2018 and its price is
not that thick, then let's see
which stocks are
available nearby.
Reliance is not available, then TCS. TCS is
quite a class of moving objects.
Next, Infosys is absolutely white,
so we can do this. Okay,
I am also getting my dam 999 below it and its 11 is also
quite below, sometimes at the right place.
How can we do this too? Hindustan
Unilever, its half is moving a little higher, but we
can wait for it, as long as we want to
take it on this side.
Devgan, its price is also coming, we
can wait for it on the upper side when  It may come
down because
Singh Sports Label
button is a value blend footwear
and PNG Hygiene is well
that somewhere TC in its demo this picture
is quite high and its virus is also quite
high so we will not consider it at all that we can
wait for Colgate Palmolive to come down in our body also.
Now we can wait a little in Asdfc Bank.
Above HDFC Bank, we will have to wait for ICICI Bank to come down in a
separate video maker and
Isai will come down in
simple ICICI Lombard
and for HDFC
Life is well
and HDFC AMC is well
that Singheshwar Bajaj Finance
's Singh is on that Kotak Mahindra Bank
then Puju latest is well for Asian Paints is
well
and Berger Paint Royal
so on Pocket Lite
's report of Industries Titan is also quite
high. Tonti Morning Ambedkar our
battery which is more than this, it is
running on the upper side, right now it is above the holiday,
Vansh's is much above you but available at 120
in Ansh Daan Whirlpool The Sun Pharma  Bajaj Auto
and from then on it is not like that the
RS of all these companies will not go very high,
if you look at their records
you will see that it always comes down,
wherever you look, that means
you can go here, here you
can see that you can set targets and exit
easily, whenever it goes down, it
definitely goes down, whenever it goes down, it definitely comes down, so there is nothing to worry about in this,
you should
not take any decision in haste, you have to be patient
and you have to take the base plate of your strategy in order
to protect your money and
whenever you add stocks available at the
movie West Indies, the refusal will be
available around 630, you
can add such stocks to your portfolio
and while adding them to the bundle, you
must keep in mind that your portfolio should be
diversified, now it remains similar,
like you will select deep people in the
Indian cricket team,
not all of them are good, they are not bowlers, they are not all-
rounders, they are a mixture of
some batsmen.  There are some bowlers, some
grinders, some spin bowlers. If you say something,
you have to keep your portfolio in a Wi-Fi mode.
If any company or
any sector is underperforming, you
can clear its deadlock right now and take your profile to a
positive level. This is the
third rule of money. You have to protect your back capital. To do this,
you have to keep your portfolio diversified.
And now it is also like this that if you buy this company
automatically, it will start going up from the very next day.
Sometimes it will also happen that
when you buy, it will go down by ten, fifteen, twenty
percent. Here you should know
that you have bought on fundamentals content,
so you have to be patient.
You have to wait for the price to come back up
and you have to exit this company only at your target.
You should not be too greedy
that you have achieved the target well. Even then, if
you stay in that company, then
you do not have to regret later that half a
minute had passed before the target was
achieved.
For this money, we have to follow
our own decisions and
add the complete to our portfolio. So
I hope you like this video, please do share
and subscribe so that your friends who are app
related can also get this help. You will
help them in getting the information.
So till then, I have been wasted and
motivated. Thank you, bye-bye.